Bastard!
Lieutenant Marito!
All units spread out!
Didn't work.
I thought that if it was going to be using lightning,
it might have been an opening for us while it was switching over.
I don't think it's going to be that easy for us.
That being the case, what are the options?
Lieutenant Marito!
Message from the Deutalian.
HQ has ordered us to pull out.
Pull out? Wait, everyone?
Dale's Platoon and Orlov's Platoon should have gotten the order by now, too.
But...
But what?
Retreat! Retreat!
No, Dale's 2-2!
Where is he? Where's the enemy?
Commander!
That invisible cataphrac we didn't take down is over there!
Crap!
Clydesdale leader to Orlov leader!
Do you read me?
Retreat!
This is Orlov leader.
It's too late.
I'm the only one...
Left over here!
Lightning...
invisibility...
There must be...
another one.
Their orders are to continue...
encircle...
and then eliminate.
By your command, my lord.
My lord.
Princess of Salem!
What's this?
I've done all I could.
It was the best I could do.
I'm sorry...
Slain.
This cannot be...
you.
No!
Thank you.
Now, young Kai's come!
Now you can all move out.
That cloud of smoke will hamper the enemy's vision for the time being.
Go!
Roger!
Also, this smoke will help us so we can attack.
I've got him.
To your right, look out!
Mustang leader!
What's going on, Kaizuka?
I thought your job was to keep lightning elsewhere.
Sorry, lieutenant.
Suddenly, its focus just completely shifted.
As if it knew where you were.
Crap!
Are we surrounded?
Looks that way.
The Deucalion!
Damage report.
We're okay, ma'am.
The charge dissipated.
Set us down.
We're extracting our cataphracts.
Right here, ma'am?
We're in the middle of the enemy.
Just land us.
Our airspeed is not optimal.
There's a tailwind.
You're descending too fast.
We're okay.
The Alt-Noah Drive can take it.
Anti-grad device to maximum.
365 meters per second descent rate.
You get aboard.
The Gaiden deals, platoon.
Now hurry!
Open the ventral hatch.
Get those cataphracts inside.
Enemy closing in.
Hostile cataphracts.
Inbound at or nine o'clock.
Main guns, fire.
Cataphract retrieval complete, Captain.
Let's go.
What is that?
Another enemy cataphract, Aft.
Same type as the one we just destroyed.
Reinforcements?
Now there's another one.
They are not support troops.
I think they're...
Radar returns.
There's 12.
24.
Numbers increasing.
Duplication ability?
All engines ahead, both!
Damn it!
Wither radar, doubler radar, both are offline.
Not good.
Invisible Zero must have messed up our entire electrical system.
Radio's out too.
GPS displays on the fritz.
And 2D radar is offline.
What do we do?
Keep it together.
Continue the ascent.
Aye, aye, ma'am.
So we are both clear.
Are you willing to swear your loyalty to Count Troyard?
Yes.
Then I shall immediately inform him.
There is a favor I would like to ask of you.
Yes, what is it?
Is an audience with Princesses Salem a possibility?
You wish to see her highness?
Yes.
And if possible, with Count Troyard.
That is no small request, my lord.
I will endeavor to see that you are accommodated.
However, a task of this nature does come at a price.
Understood, my lord.
I must say, after difficulties such as yours, another man might have lost his way.
Being seen well by the Count, in addition to Princesses of Salem, would be most beneficial.
However, do not wear ambition on your sleeve.
There is a chance it could cause you to stumble.
We're saying.
That is not the real Princesses of Salem.
I'm going into space.
Prepare a shuttle.
Congratulations on your victory, my lord slain.
No cause for celebration.
Not when the enemy escaped us.
You did achieve the objective of securing territory.
Is that not sufficient success?
This will certainly cause more knights to swear loyalty.
We must not be complacent.
There are very few things less reliable than a knight's loyalty.
We know that well, my lord.
Now, my lord.
Concerning that request from Count Borocruz.
How shall I reply to him?
Very well, my lord.
Mazurak, was that his name?
If he wishes to see the princess, we will let him.
She seems to be quite happy with her role of further extending our base of power.
At least, for the time being.
This is bad.
And it's way past any quick and easy patch.
I hate this.
Night vision's out of whack also.
So I don't even dare to try to fly by eye.
Where's the problem?
Is it in the sensor system?
That's very good, Ensign Kaisuka.
How did you know that?
The signs are there.
It's faint, but the fuselage is still holding a charge.
A malfunction with the engine isn't very likely with this vessel.
In which case...
Well, can you do anything about it?
We can't fly like this.
Well, you might want to try dropping a little lower.
Just enough to get us below enemy radar.
But now that I can't use the GPWS or the altimeter, I'm scared of approaching the ground.
There's no reason to worry.
We're at 9,200.
You can really measure that just by looking?
Can you also get VOR stations?
Yes.
Once you have both signals, let me know, okay?
Then I'll calculate our radial.
Sure.
What's our heading?
I was trying to put us on 110.
And you're almost there now.
Maintain a vector offset.
Three degrees for two minutes.
This is not good.
Are we caught in some kind of nasty turbulence?
This goes on a while.
Let's adjust our speed.
No, I've got it.
I think I can handle this.
Like earlier.
I see that.
Well, I guess experience is really what's needed here now.
I'll let you know when I pick up an LLZ.
Thanks.
Thank you for that.
Maybe we should be the ones who are thanking you.
Though Lieutenant Marito said he was just shocked that you would do something so crazy.
I do not want to hear that from you.
Tell him that was my reply.
That is good to hear.
So then, preparations for the founding are all proceeding smoothly?
Yes.
I can barely stand this awful wait for this new kingdom's birth.
And then to see your home world at long last.
Merely a world inhabited by vulgar trash.
Hardly the restful image conjured up by the word home.
Actually, I never really had a place that felt like home.
And actually, neither did I.
Not on verse, nor in royal eminence.
Has there ever been a way for me to find solace?
But now, Slane, anywhere that I can be with you, in any circumstance, that is my home.
You honor me.
I shall call on you again later.
But Slane, can't you stay a little longer?
So sorry, Highness.
But matters require my attention.
Please forgive me.
Inaho!
Oh, Inka.
What's going on?
Yesterday, Nina was going on about you being on the bridge.
And helping them out up there.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Uh, Inaho?
Is there something wrong?
Like what?
Come on, what do you mean what?
Maybe it's nothing, but...
What do you think about the enemy coordinating their attack like that?
Maybe it's been so hard they're forced to swallow their pride and work together.
Judging by the outcome, I don't think we have that much to fear from it.
Well, then, do you suppose it's connected to that proclamation?
That orbital knight slain Troyard is the one behind Princess of Salem.
Even young Kaisuke seems to think he's something special.
If this opponent is setting things into motion with a specific goal in mind, it's certainly not some simple scheme we can counter with superior resources.
Enter.
PFC Matsuribi with a message.
Dispatch from HQ, ma'am.
A request for reinforcements?
Launch all-out attack on newly captured territory.
Take it back.
So they can use us as bait?
That's what it sounds like.
And how have you been feeling since then?
Well, physically, just fine.
As to my memory, however, it is a little hazy, I have to admit.
Hardly surprising.
The fact that you came back to consciousness, that was a miracle.
Perhaps, you should not try to force yourself to remember.
Thank you, Slain, very much.
I fear I must take my leave now.
Try to get some rest, please.
Yes.
Look after Her Highness until I return.
Milord, do you have a moment?
I believe I know what you wish to ask.
The proclamation, yes?
Taking me as her husband, founding a new kingdom.
That proclamation issued by Princess Lemrina
was simply a direct result of the weakness in my heart.
Princess Asalem is going to wake up.
I tried to hold on to that belief, but was unable to in the end.
I had given up, deep inside somewhere.
It was then that the miracle came to pass,
as if to reprimand me for being such a fool.
Now, of course, things are completely different.
And so my focus, therefore, must now be on how best to keep Her Highness happy.
Only that, and nothing else.
But my lord, what of Princess Lemrina?
As to what she hopes the future will hold,
I believe I have an idea.
I think that she wishes the same thing I do.
A place where she can find some solace.
But I fear that to be something that we would never be able to achieve together.
So now may not be the time to tell her everything.
And even if she looks down on me,
or if she has no respect for what I'm doing here,
it doesn't mean anything to me anyway.
It is so ironic.
I had waited so desperately for Her Highness to awaken.
But now I, I hope that her memory never returns.
My lord, your willingness and resolve to serve my trusted Count Troyard fills me with such joy that I cannot contain it.
Your Highness is extremely gracious.
I am determined and fully prepared to serve both your Highness and Count Troyard with wholehearted devotion.
I, too, was deeply moved by Count Mazurak's unwavering allegiance and personal strength,
as he swore to escape and rise up once again in the name of verse,
even as he was being held prisoner.
Begging your pardon, Highness.
I am given to understand that you yourself were subjected to similar hardships during your stay on Earth.
Yes, the situation was similar, and the Terrans are all vulgar trash in so many ways.
There was not even a single one where your Highness might have grown close?
I would never do such a thing.
My handmaiden had the task of interacting with them if necessary.
There once was a time when I entertained the notion of reconciling with those people.
A foolish idea, quickly discarded.
Why is Slain not here to help at a time like this?
Pardon, Your Highness.
Lord Slain has many preparations to oversee for the war.
He said as much to me earlier.
He is too absent, locking himself away in his castle too much.
Whatever he's doing, can he not do it here?
I am told that it is due to precious resources.
Well then, I shall go to him.
Please, Your Highness.
Yes, that's it.
I'll go to his landing castle.
No, Your Highness.
Are you injured, Highness?
Are you hurt?
A thousand pardons.
Just how long will it be?
Please, how long will it be?
Let me see you to your room, Highness.
Please, pardon the delay.
My Lord Count Mazurek, would you please follow me to the parlor?
Now that my credentials have been thoroughly checked...
My deep apologies.
Oh, not at all.
The blunder here is mine.
To think I allowed my ship to break down.
How fortunate for me I was in your vicinity.
So I guess that Count Troyard is still working over at the moon base?
Yes.
I regret you cannot see him.
But Lord Harklight is on his way and ought to be here soon.
I made certain they were gone before I did this.
Troyard is coming back here from the moon base a lot more than is really necessary.
Meaning that Princess of Salem must be.
My Lord, if you would please wait here.
Hmm?
Are those Terran flowers?
Yes.
It's obvious this castle has undergone quite the transformation.
You can see that, my Lord?
I was acquainted with its former master.
He detested all things Terran, fearing that they might be harboring microorganisms.
Oh, certainly there is no such problem.
Terran flowers are safe.
Oh, so then you have been down there.
No, just repeating what I have been told.
I had heard Princess of Salem had a personal attendant, but I did not expect...
Is it you?
No, I'm not.
I mean, when Her Highness went to Earth, she was all alone.
I'm so sorry.
We were not speaking of Earth, were we?
Please, I must be going.
You can honestly say you have not been there.
That you truly do not know what happened?
What about a boy named Inaho Kaisuka?
How long will it be?
Tell me, sister.
How long will it take?
For you to release your grip on his feelings.
How long?
He brought this for me?
Yes, m'lady.
He said he wished it to be presented to you in particular.
To the princess who knew about Earth is what he said.
Ah.
Oh, m'lady.
I... remember.
All of it.
Soukous...
I don't know.
Maybe you might...
Yeah.
I look.
As we come along...
Thank you.